{
    "id": "f1cfaf4c84be4e5fa326327d63e917e2",
    "title": "Would rather, had better, I wish",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1210f5cb0aec4ff1b6f32d06c4ee54f2",
            "title": "Would Rather, Had Better, I Wish",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I would rather you ………………….. see her anymore.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't",
                        "didn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ……………….. speak Spanish.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ……………….. your ways.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "mended",
                        "mend",
                        "to mend"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ………………. to university.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have gone",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish tomorrow ……………. Sunday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you ………………. stop smoking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you …………………. be quiet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish it ………………… stop raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would rather …………………. on the weekend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to not work",
                        "not work",
                        "not to work"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We had better ………………… for him or we will be late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not wait",
                        "not to wait",
                        "to not wait"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}